A Guide to the Correspondence Files of Special Collections, University of Virginia Library 1931-1990s
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence (General)
  - Rare Books Dept. Correspondence (miscellaneous)
    - Glen, James (Box A35-15Q)
    - Glenn, Mrs. Frank (Box A35-15Q)
    - Goals and Objectives - Departmental (Box A35-15Q)
    - Goals and Objectives - Library (Box A35-15Q)
    - Goals and Objectives - University (Box A35-15Q)
    - Goff, Frederick (see also Library of Congress) (Box A35-15Q)
    - Goldsmith, Oliver (Box A35-15Q)
    - Goldstone, Adrian (Box A35-15Q)
    - Gooch, Richard E. (Box A35-15Q)
    - Gordon, Armistead (Box A35-15Q)
    - Gordon, Judge Bennett T. - estate of (Box A35-15Q)
    - Gordon, John (Box A35-15Q)
    - Gordon Douglas Dinner (Box A35-15Q)
    - Gordon, William (Box A35-15Q)
    - Gosnell, Fred A., Sr. (Box A35-15Q)
    - Gothic Novel (Box A35-15Q)
    - Gott, John K. (Box A35-15Q)
    - Grammars - Virginia (see also Textbooks) (Box A35-15R)
    - Grandstaff, Coleman (Box A35-15R)
    - Graphic Arts (Box A35-15R)
    - Grases, Pedro (Box A35-15R)
    - Graves, Harold E. (Box A35-15R)
    - Graves, Joseph C. (Box A35-15R)
    - Graves, Walter Raleigh (Box A35-15R)
    - Gray Commission (Box A35-15R)
    - Great Northern Railway (Box A35-15R)
    - Green Julien (Box A35-15R)
    - Greer, Louise (Box A35-15R)
    - de Graffenreid (Box A35-15R)
    - Griffin, Lloyd (Box A35-15R)
    - Griffin, William M. (Box A35-15R)
    - Grinnalds, Mrs. Jefferson C. (Box A35-15R)
    - Grolier Club Exhibition (Box A35-15R)
    - Grolier Club - Herman Melville 150th Anniversary Exhibition (Box A35-15R)
    - Grolier Club - thank you letters / regrets, & acknowledgement of gifts (Box A35-15R)
    - Grolier Club (Box A35-15R)
    - Grolier Club Notices (Box A35-15R)
    - Bibliographical Society Grolier Club cannot attend 1958 (Box A35-15R)
    - Bibliographical Society Grolier Club will attend 1958 (Box A35-15R)
    - Guggenheim Productions, Inc. (Box A35-15R)
    - Gulden, Charles (Box A35-15R)
    - Gunter, Bradley (Box A35-15R)
    - Gutenburg Bible (Box A35-15R)
    - Groner, Duncan (Box A35-15R)
    - Gunter, Susan Hart (Mrs. J. Bradley Hunt) (Box A35-15R)
    - H - General 1959-1986 (Box A35-15S)
    - Hakluyt Society (Box A35-15S)
    - Hale, Edward Everett (Box A35-15S)
    - Hale, Laura Virginia (Box A35-15S)
    - Hale, Ralph (Box A35-15S)
    - Hall, Verna M. (Box A35-15S)
    - Hall, Wilmer L. (Box A35-15S)
    - Hall of Fame (Box A35-15S)
    - Hallenbeck, Chester T. (Box A35-15S)
    - Hallock, Mrs. Harold (Box A35-15S)
    - Hamilton, Charles (Box A35-15S)
    - Hamilton, Sally W. (Box A35-15S)
    - Hamlin, Percy G. (Box A35-15S)
    - Hampden-Sidney College (Box A35-15S)
    - Hanak, Walter K. (Slavic bibliographer) (Box A35-15S)
    - Hanaway, Mrs. William L. (Box A35-15S)
    - Handrea, Mihai H. (Box A35-15S)
    - Handy, E.S.C. (Box A35-15S)
    - Hanson, L.W. (see also Bodleian Library) (Box A35-15S)
    - Hard, Elizabeth W. (Box A35-15S)
    - Harding, Walter (Box A35-15S)
    - Hardy, Grahame (Box A35-15S)
    - Hargrett, Felix (see also Emily Barksdale) (Box A35-15S)
    - Harmsen, Tyrus G. (see also A.L.A.) (Box A35-15S)
    - Harper & Brothers (Box A35-15S)
    - Harper, Lathrop C. (see also Douglas Personage) (Box A35-15T)
    - Harrer, John A. (Box A35-15T)
    - Harrison, J. Hartwell (Box A35-15T)
    - Harrison, Mrs. Kay (Box A35-15T)
    - Harrisse Collection (Box A35-15T)
    - Harrison, Nellie M. (Pickney) (Box A35-15T)
    - Hart, James H. (Box A35-15T)
    - Harte, Bret (Box A35-15T)
    - Harvard University and Library (see also Jacob Blanck) (Box A35-15T)
    - Harvey, Lashley G. (Box A35-15T)
    - Harwell, Richard B. (Box A35-15T)
    - Hawaii Imprints (Box A35-15T)
    - Hawthorne, Nathaniel (Box A35-15T)
    - Hawthorne's Scarlet Letter (Box A35-15T)
    - Hay, Mary Oakley (Box A35-15T)
    - Hayman, David (Box A35-15T)
    - Haynes, Donald R. (Box A35-15T)
    - Healey, George H. (Box A35-15T)
    - Health and Welfare Services (Box A35-15T)
    - Heaney, Howell J. (see also Rudolph Hirsch) (Box A35-15T)
    - Hearn, Lafcadio (Box A35-15T)
    - Heath, Peter (Box A35-15T)
    - Heavin Family (Box A35-15T)
    - Heilborn, George (Box A35-15T)
    - Heiskell, John (see also Winchester Imprints) (Box A35-15T)
    - Helms, James (Box A35-15T)
    - Helvetius (Box A35-15T)
    - Hemphill, W. Edwin (Box A35-15T)
    - Hench, Atcheson (Box A35-15T)
    - Henderson, Charles (Box A35-15T)
    - Henings Statutes (Box A35-15T)
    - Henneman, Mrs. Richard H. (Box A35-15T)
    - Henry, O. (Box A35-15T)
    - Henry, Patrick (Box A35-16A)
    - Henty, George A. (Box A35-16A)
    - Herbals (Box A35-16A)
    - Herbs (Box A35-16A)
    - Hereford, President (Box A35-16A)
    - Hermann map (Box A35-16A)
    - Herrick, Samuel (Box A35-16A)
    - Hertz uncatalogued pamphlets (Box A35-16A)
    - Higginson, Mrs. John M. (Box A35-16A)
    - Hinman, Charlton (Box A35-16A)
    - Hinman machine (Box A35-16A)
    - Hinton, J. William (Box A35-16A)
    - Hinton, Mrs. Lottie J. (see also Virginia H. Dillon) (Box A35-16A)
    - Hirsch, Eric D., Jr. (Box A35-16A)
    - Hjorth, John T. (Box A35-16A)
    - Hirsch, Rudolph (see also Howell J. Heany) (Box A35-16A)
    - Historic Annapolis, Inc. (Box A35-16A)
    - Historical Societies (Box A35-16A)
    - Hobbs, Horton (Box A35-16A)
    - Hodges, John, Jr. (Box A35-16A)
    - Hoes, Laurence G. (Box A35-16A)
    - Hofer, Philip (Box A35-16A)
    - Holiday Schedule and Payrolls (Box A35-16A)
    - Hollinger Corporation (Box A35-16A)
    - Hollins College Library (Box A35-16A)
    - Holmes, Sherlock (Box A35-16A)
    - Holmes, Thomas J. (Box A35-16A)
    - Holzbaur, Frederick J. (Box A35-16A)
    - Honor System [University of Virginia] (Box A35-16A)
    - Horace (see also Jefferson Books - A. W.Machen) (Box A35-16A)
    - Horne, Bernard S. (see also Pittsburgh Bibliophiles) (Box A35-16A)
    - Hotchner, Aaron E. (Box A35-16A)
    - Hotels (Box A35-16A)
    - Houchens, William C. (Box A35-16A)
    - Hourly, part-time and temporary employees (Box A35-16A)
    - House of Whittemore (see also Barrett Orders) (Box A35-16A)
    - Housekeeping (Box A35-16A)
    - Howard, Carter Eugene (Box A35-16A)
    - I - General 1960-1974 (Box A35-16B)
    - I.B.M. type manual (Box A35-16B)
    - Imprint Society (Box A35-16B)
    - Imprints: Singers Glen, Virginia (Box A35-16B)
    - Incunabula (see also E.J. McShane) (Box A35-16B)
    - India (Box A35-16B)
    - Indiana University (Box A35-16B)
    - (Box A35-16B)
    - Indiana University - Howells (Box A35-16B)
    - Indiana University - Lilly Library (Box A35-16B)
    - Information Services Group (Box A35-16B)
    - Ingram Mrs. E.B. or Margaret Jane Foglesong (Box A35-16B)
    - Ink - Offsetting (Box A35-16B)
    - Ingram, Thomas J. (Box A35-16B)
    - Inserts (Box A35-16B)
    - Insurance programs (Box A35-16B)
    - Insurance - Rare Books (Box A35-16B)
    - Insurance schedule - Initial Report (Box A35-16B)
    - Internal Routing and Mail Service (Box A35-16C)
    - Insurance (Box A35-16C)
    - International Congress of Bibliophiles (Box A35-16C)
    - Invoices (Box A35-16C)
    - Invoice Copies (Box A35-16C)
    - Irish Literature (Box A35-16C)
    - Irving, John Treat (Box A35-16C)
    - Irving, Washington (Box A35-16C)
    - Ishill (Box A35-16C)
    - Italy (Box A35-16C)
    - Italian flood relief (Box A35-16C)
    - Ivy, Edward L., Jr. (Box A35-16C)
    - J - General (Box A35-16C)
    - Jackson, Donald (Box A35-16C)
    - Jackson, Elsie F. (Box A35-16C)
    - Jackson, Stonewall (Box A35-16C)
    - Jackson, W.A. (Box A35-16C)
    - Jaffe, Mrs. Louis I. (Box A35-16C)
    - Henry James Exhibition (Box A35-16C)
    - James, Mrs. H.M., Jr. (Box A35-16C)
    - Janssen, A. Patton (Box A35-16D)
    - Japanese Books (Box A35-16D)
    - Jarman Printing Co. (Box A35-16D)
    - Jayne, Sears (Box A35-16D)
    - Joynes Books (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson, Isaac (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson, Lucy (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson - Manual of Parliamentary Practice (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson Papers of University of Virginia (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson Papers on University of Virginia (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson Printing (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson Silver (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Notes on Virginia (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Religious views (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Summary View (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson, Thomas (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson, Thomas - Fine Arts Library (Box A35-16D)
    - Jeffersonian Americana (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson - Wirt correspondence (Box A35-16D)
    - Jeffress, Mrs. Robert M. (Box A35-16D)
    - Jefferson - Hemings (Box A35-16D)
    - Jenkins, Paul (see also Presonnel Office) (Box A35-16D)
    - Jennings, John M. (Box A35-16D)
    - Jitney Bus (Box A35-16D)
    - Job Descriptions (Box A35-16D)
    - Job Descriptions - Classified (Box A35-16D)
    - Johnson, Harold B., Jr. (Box A35-16D)
    - Johnson, Samuel (Box A35-16E)
    - Johnson, Justice William (Box A35-16E)
    - Johnson Reprint Corporation (Box A35-16E)
    - Johnston Clem D. (Box A35-16E)
    - Johnston, George Burke (Box A35-16E)
    - Johnson, James - School textbooks collection (Box A35-16E)
    - Johnston, Mr. & Mrs. James D. (Box A35-16E)
    - Johnston, Mrs. Ladd (Box A35-16E)
    - Johnston, Mrs. Russell Z. (Box A35-16E)
    - Joint Special Collections Reading Room (Box A35-16E)
    - Jones Library (Box A35-16E)
    - Jones, Archer (Box A35-16E)
    - Jones, T. Catesby (Box A35-16E)
    - Catesby Jones Collection (see also Art Exhibits) (Box A35-16E)
    - Jones, Col. Charles C. (Box A35-16E)
    - Jones, Gordon W. (Box A35-16E)
    - Jones, Hugh (Box A35-16E)
    - Jones, Joseph (Box A35-16E)
    - Judy, R.D. (Box A35-16E)
    - Junius (Box A35-16E)
    - Juveniles (Box A35-16E)
    - K - General (Box A35-16F)
    - Kable, William S. (Box A35-16F)
    - Kane, Harnett (Box A35-16F)
    - Kane, Ms. R. Keith (Box A35-16F)
    - Kansas University library (Box A35-16F)
    - Kaplan William - books (Box A35-16F)
    - Kaulback, Frank S., Jr. (Box A35-16F)
    - The Peter Kavanagh Hand Press (Box A35-16F)
    - Kean, Robert H. (Box A35-16F)
    - Keeler, Fanny (Box A35-16F)
    - Kees, Weldon (Box A35-16F)
    - Kelleher, William F. (Box A35-16F)
    - Kelly, Mrs. John J. (Box A35-16F)
    - Kendall, Paul (Box A35-16F)
    - Kendig, Perry F. (Box A35-16F)
    - Kent State University (Box A35-16F)
    - Kentucky, University of (Box A35-16F)
    - Ketham, Johannes de (Box A35-16F)
    - Key, Francis Scott (Box A35-16F)
    - Khayyam, Omar (Box A35-16F)
    - Kidd, Hari (Box A35-16F)
    - Kilpatrick, Jack (Box A35-16F)
    - Kimball, David A. (Box A35-16F)
    - Kimball, Fiske (Box A35-16F)
    - Kimball, Marie (Box A35-16F)
    - King, Clyde (Box A35-16F)
    - Kingston Galleries (Box A35-16F)
    - Kinne, Mrs. Gerald (Box A35-16F)
    - Kinsey, Lewis P. (Box A35-16G)
    - Kipling, Rudyard (Box A35-16G)
    - Kirgo, George (Box A35-16G)
    - Kirkham, E. Bruce (Box A35-16G)
    - Kluge - Carriage Museum (Box A35-16G)
    - Knapp, Mary E. (Box A35-16G)
    - Knickerbocker, K.K. (Box A35-16G)
    - Knipp Company, Inc. (Box A35-16G)
    - Koda, Paul S. (Box A35-16G)
    - Knoedler Art Galleries (W.F. Davidson) (Box A35-16G)
    - Knopf, Alfred A., Inc. (Box A35-16G)
    - Kohn, John Van E. (see also Seven Gables Bookshop) (Box A35-16G)
    - Kramer, Sidney (Box A35-16G)
    - Kraus, H.P. (see also Helmut Lehmann-Haupt) (Box A35-16G)
    - Kress Library (Box A35-16G)
    - Krumm, Robert A. (Box A35-16G)
    - Matti Kurjensaari (Box A35-16G)
    - L - General (Box A35-16G)
    - Lada-Mocarski, V. (Box A35-16G)
    - Lafayette (Box A35-16G)
    - Lakeside Classics (Box A35-16G)
    - Lakeside Press (see also McGregor binding - Macdonald) (Box A35-16G)
    - Land, Miss Roy (Box A35-16G)
    - Lands U.S. (Box A35-16G)
    - Lang, Andrew (Box A35-16G)
    - Langhorne, Elizabeth Coles (Box A35-16G)
    - Langhorne Sisters (Box A35-16G)
    - Lasner, Mark Samuels (Box A35-16H)
    - Latham, Edward Connery (Box A35-16H)
    - Latin American Studies (Box A35-16H)
    - Law, Andrew (bibliography) (Box A35-16H)
    - Law Books (Box A35-16H)
    - Law Library - Larry Wenger (Box A35-16H)
    - Lawn Society (Box A35-16H)
    - Lawrence, D.H. (Box A35-16H)
    - Lazare, Edward (Box A35-16H)
    - Leamington Book Shop (Box A35-16H)
    - Lederer (Box A35-16H)
    - Lederer, John (Box A35-16H)
    - Lee, Edwin Gray (Box A35-16H)
    - Lee, Lawrence (Box A35-16H)
    - Leftwich, James A. (Box A35-16H)
    - Le Gear (Box A35-16H)
    - Lehman, Mrs. Edwin P. (Box A35-16H)
    - Lehmann-Haupt, Helmut (see also H.P. Kraus) (Box A35-16H)
    - Lesley, Theodore (Box A35-16H)
    - L'estrange, Roger (Box A35-16H)
    - Letcher, John (Box A35-16H)
    - The Letters of Shahcoolen (Box A35-16H)
    - Levenson, Roger (Box A35-16H)
    - Levin, David (Box A35-16H)
    - Levin, Harry (Box A35-16H)
    - Levy Family (Box A35-16H)
    - Lewis, James F., Jr. (Box A35-16H)
    - Lewis, Wilmarth (Box A35-16H)
    - Lexington Intelligenter (Box A35-16H)
    - Librarian's Institute (Box A35-16H)
    - Libraries - Federal Aid (Box A35-16H)
    - Libraries - special announcements (Box A35-16H)
    - Library Annual Report 1967-1968 (Box A35-16H)
    - Library - Building Program (Box A35-16H)
    - Library Cards (charge & discharge) (Box A35-16H)
    - Library Committee (Box A35-16H)
    - Library Committee - Faculty status (Box A35-16H)
    - Library Committee - Faculty status (Box A35-16I)
    - Library Letterhead (Box A35-16I)
    - Library of Congress (Box A35-16I)
    - Library of Congress - Card Division (Box A35-16I)
    - Library of Congress - Documents Division (Box A35-16I)
    - Library of Congress - Exhibit (Box A35-16I)
    - Library of Congress - Descriptive Card Cataloguing (Box A35-16I)
    - Library of Congress (Box A35-16I)
    - Library of Congress - Music Division (Box A35-16I)
    - Library of Congress - Presidential papers (Box A35-16I)
    - Library of Congress - Schwegmann, G. (see also photodupl.) (Box A35-16I)
    - Library of Congress - Union Catalogue (see also Imprints / cities & towns) (Box A35-16I)
    - Library Orientation (Box A35-16I)
    - Library Research (Box A35-16I)
    - Library Signs (Box A35-16I)
    - The Library - Union Theological Seminary (Box A35-16I)
    - Libraries - Charlotesville & Albemarle (Box A35-16I)
    - Liebert, Herman W. (Box A35-16I)
    - Lighting (Box A35-16I)
    - Lilly Library (Box A35-16I)
    - Lindner (Box A35-16I)
    - Lincoln (Box A35-16I)
    - Lindsay, Mrs. J. Gordon (Box A35-16I)
    - Vachel Lindsay - Barrett Gift 1974 (Box A35-16J)
    - Linedex (Box A35-16J)
    - Little Magazines (Box A35-16J)
    - Little, William A. (Box A35-16J)
    - Livingston, S.K. (Box A35-16J)
    - Lloyd, John Uri (Box A35-16J)
    - Location Symbols (Box A35-16J)
    - Locke, Charles (Box A35-16J)
    - Locked Stacks (Box A35-16J)
    - Looney, Mrs. William B. (Box A35-16J)
    - Los Angeles Book Auction Gallery (Box A35-16J)
    - Lost Cause Press (Box A35-16J)
    - Lost Cause Press - Clark's Travels Vol. 3 (Box A35-16J)
    - Lost Cause Press - Clark's Travels Project (1957- ) (Box A35-16J)
    - Lost Cause Press - Yellow Slip Lists (Box A35-16J)
    - Loundsbury, Elizabeth (Box A35-16J)
    - Lovell, Bill (Box A35-16J)
    - Lowdermilk, W.H., & Co. (Box A35-16J)
    - Lucker-Freeman (Library Study Committee) (Box A35-16J)
    - Lucretius (Box A35-16J)
    - Lurie, Bernice S. (Box A35-16J)
    - Lux, Robert A. (Box A35-16J)
    - Lydenberg, H.M. (Box A35-16J)
    - Lynchburg (Box A35-16J)
    - M - General 1957-1986 (Box A35-16K)
    - MacDonald, James Co. (Box A35-16K)
    - MacKenzie, Alan F.S. (Box A35-16K)
    - Malone, Dumas (Box A35-16K)
    - Mackay-Smith, A. (Box A35-16L)
    - Management Development Program (Box A35-16L)
    - Manuals - Remington standard typewriter (Box A35-16L)
    - Martin, Richard (Skip) (Box A35-16L)
    - Mary Baldwin College (Box A35-16L)
    - Maryland Historical Society (Box A35-16L)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society (Box A35-16L)
    - McAleer, E.A. (Box A35-16L)
    - McAlister, Mrs. J. Worth (Box A35-16L)
    - McCabe, W. Gordon - Library 1978-1987 (Box A35-16L)
    - McClary, Jane (Box A35-16L)
    - McClellan, Stephen / McConnell, James (Box A35-16L)
    - McCorison, Marcus A. (Box A35-16L)
    - McCowat - Mercer Press, Inc. (Box A35-16L)
    - McConnell, Jim (Box A35-16L)
    - McDonald, Cornelia (Truluck Books) (Box A35-16L)
    - McFarland, Carl (Box A35-16L)
    - McGuire, Mrs. Hunter H. (Box A35-16L)
    - McIntosh, John (Box A35-16L)
    - McKenzie, D.F. (Box A35-16L)
    - McKeon, Newton F. (Box A35-16L)
    - MciKnight, Mr.& Mrs. F.H. (Box A35-16L)
    - McLean, Robert (Box A35-16L)
    - McLean, Ruari (Box A35-16L)
    - McManaway, James G. (Box A35-16L)
    - McMath, Neil (Box A35-16L)
    - McNally, James (Box A35-16L)
    - McShane, E.S. (see also Incunabula) (Box A35-16L)
    - Maas, Katherine (Box A35-16L)
    - Mabbott, Thomas O. (Box A35-16L)
    - Madison, James (Box A35-16L)
    - Madison, James - Library (see also Scott) (Box A35-16L)
    - Madison - map (Box A35-16L)
    - Magellan (Box A35-16L)
    - Mallet, John W. (Box A35-16M)
    - Manusco, Rev. Laurence (Box A35-16M)
    - Manheim Collection (Box A35-16M)
    - Manierre, William R., II (Box A35-16M)
    - Manning, (Mrs.) Van H. (Box A35-16M)
    - Maps (Box A35-16M)
    - Maps - Cataloguing (Box A35-16M)
    - Maps - Japan (Box A35-16M)
    - Maps - Mounting (Box A35-16M)
    - Maps - Washington (Box A35-16M)
    - Marks, Wirt P., Jr. (Box A35-16M)
    - Marshall, Richard C. (Box A35-16M)
    - Marlyn Book Company (Box A35-16M)
    - Marshall, Irene H. (Box A35-16M)
    - Martin, Joseph (Box A35-16M)
    - Martin, Roy C. (Box A35-16M)
    - Marvell, Andrew (Box A35-16M)
    - Maryland Council for Higher Education (Box A35-16M)
    - Mary Washington College Library (Box A35-16M)
    - Maryland Imprints (see also Roger P. Bristol) (Box A35-16M)
    - Mason and Dixon (Box A35-16M)
    - Massey, Linton (1947- ) (Box A35-16M)
    - Mrs. Massey - Faulkner exhibition (Box A35-16M)
    - Massey, Mrs. Linton (Mary) (Box A35-16M)
    - Maggs Brothers, Ltd. (Box A35-16M)
    - MagnaCarta (Box A35-16M)
    - Mailing Lists - Misc. (Box A35-16M)
    - Malkin, Sol (Box A35-16M)
    - Massey, Mrs. Linton R. (Box A35-16M)
    - Masterson, James R. (Box A35-16M)
    - Maternity Leave (Box A35-16M)
    - Mathematics (Box A35-16M)
    - Mather (Box A35-16M)
    - Mather, Cotton (Box A35-16M)
    - Maxfield, Brent (Box A35-16M)
    - Maxwell, R.D. (Box A35-16M)
    - Maxwell, R.D., Jr. (Box A35-16M)
    - Mayo, Mrs. Bernard - McLeod Deposit (Box A35-16M)
    - Mays, D.J. (see also Edmund Pendleton) (Box A35-16M)
    - Meacham, Harry M. (Box A35-16M)
    - Mead, Frank D. (Box A35-16M)
    - Meade, Robert Douthat (Box A35-16M)
    - Meador, Edward L. (Box A35-16M)
    - Mechanical Equipment (Box A35-16M)
    - Medals (Box A35-16M)
    - Medicine (Box A35-16M)
    - Medicine Bibliography (Box A35-16M)
    - Meeks, Bernard M. (Box A35-16M)
    - University of Melbourne (see also Australia) (Box A35-16M)
    - Melcher, Daniel - Melcher-Frost material (Box A35-16M)
    - Mellon, Paul - Collection (Box A35-16M)
    - Melville, Herman (Box A35-16O)
    - Merchants Hope Church Foundation (Box A35-16O)
    - Mergenthaler, Linotype (Box A35-16O)
    - Meridan Gravure Company (see also Harold Hugo) (Box A35-16O)
    - Merit System (Box A35-16O)
    - Meriwether, James B. (Box A35-16O)
    - Merriman, Helen A. P. (estate) (Box A35-16O)
    - Merritt, Mrs. D.M. (Box A35-16O)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box A35-16O)
    - Metzdorf (Box A35-16O)
    - Metzdorf, Robert (Box A35-16O)
    - Mexico (Box A35-16O)
    - Meyer, Edwin O. (Box A35-16O)
    - Michie, T. (Box A35-16O)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box A35-16O)
    - Mickey, Groke (Box A35-16O)
    - Microcard Corporation (Box A35-16O)
    - Microfilm Master Registration (Box A35-16O)
    - Microfilm newspapers (Box A35-16O)
    - Microprints (Box A35-16O)
    - Microprint government sales (Box A35-16O)
    - Middendorf, J. William (Box A35-16O)
    - Midwestern Books Competition (Box A35-16O)
    - Miller, Clarence H. (Box A35-16O)
    - Miller, Henry (see also Lawrence Durrell; Elmer Gertz) (Box A35-16O)
    - Miller, Henry, Jr. (see also J. Isaac Copelan) (Box A35-16O)
    - Miller, Prof. John C. (Box A35-16O)
    - Miller, Minor C. (Box A35-16O)
    - Miller, Mr. & Mrs. Paul C. (Box A35-16O)
    - Miller, Robert L. (Box A35-16O)
    - Miller & Rhoads (Box A35-16O)
    - Milton (Box A35-16O)
    - Mimeo forms for book orders (filled) (Box A35-16O)
    - Minnesota (Box A35-16O)
    - Minor, C. Venable (Box A35-16O)
    - Mish, Charles C. (Box A35-16O)
    - Missing Books (Box A35-16O)
    - Mississippi Valley Historical Assoc. (1952- ) (Box A35-16O)
    - Mobile Public Library (Box A35-16O)
    - Moffatt, L.G. (Box A35-16O)
    - Molone, Thomas S. (see also Keats; and E.A. Poe - Persius) (Box A35-16O)
    - Molyneux (Box A35-16O)
    - Monroe, James - books (Box A35-16O)
    - James Monroe Memorial Foundation (see also Laurence G. Hoes) (Box A35-16O)
    - Mooney, William A. (Box A35-16O)
    - Moore, Earl E. (Box A35-16O)
    - Moore, Ethel Vandevender (Box A35-16O)
    - Moore, Franklin L. (Box A35-16O)
    - Moran, C.E. (Box A35-16O)
    - Morgan, Wilbur P. (Box A35-16O)
    - Morley (Box A35-16O)
    - Morrill, Edward (Box A35-16O)
    - Morrison, Paul G. (Box A35-16O)
    - Morrison, Mrs. William L. (Box A35-16O)
    - Morrissett, M. Robert (Box A35-16O)
    - Morse, Frank E. - Mount Vernon Ladie's Association (Box A35-16O)
    - Morse, Jedidiah (Box A35-16O)
    - Morton, Dr. C. Bruce, II (Box A35-16O)
    - Mott, Howard S. (Box A35-16O)
    - Mott-Smith, Mrs. K.O. (Box A35-16O)
    - Mount Holyoke College (Box A35-16O)
    - Moulder, Alfred & Evelyn - Townsend Book Bindery (Box A35-16O)
    - Mount Pleasant Bookbinders (Box A35-16O)
    - Mount Vernon Ladie's Assoc. (see also George Washington) (Box A35-16O)
    - Mowinckel, Mr. & Mrs. John (Box A35-16O)
    - Moyston Estate (Box A35-16O)
    - Muller, Mrs. Rene (Box A35-16O)
    - Mummendey, Dr. R. (Box A35-16O)
    - Munford, Thomas T. (Brig. Gen.) (Box A35-16O)
    - Murfin, James V. (Box A35-16O)
    - Murphy, Mr. & Mrs. William B. (Box A35-16O)
    - Music (see also A. Mckay Smith; Benjamin R. Hanby; and Henry Clay) (Box A35-16Q)
    - Music Collections (see also Swan Collection) (Box A35-16Q)
    - Music and Music Dealers (Box A35-16Q)
    - Mystery Stories (Box A35-16Q)
    - N - General 1965-1984 (Box A35-16Q)
    - Nalle, Mr. & Mrs. John (Box A35-16Q)
    - Nash, Edward W. (Box A35-16Q)
    - National Book Awards (Box A35-16Q)
    - National Gallery of Art (Box A35-16Q)
    - National Library Bindery Co. of Georgia (Box A35-16Q)
    - National Union Catalog of Manuscript Collections (Box A35-16Q)
    - Neale, Mrs. Charles T. (Box A35-16Q)
    - Neale, Doris Kellogg (Box A35-16Q)
    - Nebenzahl, Kenneth (Box A35-16Q)
    - Netherlands, the (Box A35-16Q)
    - New Building (Box A35-16Q)
    - The Newberry Library (Box A35-16Q)
    - Newcomb, J. Churchill (Box A35-16Q)
    - Newcomb, John Lloyd (Box A35-16Q)
    - Newcomb Hall - Jerry N. Showalter (Box A35-16Q)
    - New Jersey Imprints (Box A35-16Q)
    - Newspaper Microfilm (Box A35-16Q)
    - Newspapers (Box A35-16Q)
    - New York Historical Society (Box A35-16R)
    - New York Public Library (Box A35-16R)
    - New York Times (Box A35-16R)
    - New York Times Book Review Orders (Box A35-16R)
    - New York University (Box A35-16R)
    - New York University Press (Box A35-16R)
    - Noland, Eleanor (Box A35-16R)
    - Noland, Mrs. William C. (Box A35-16R)